Finding Aid for the Al Pearce Papers PASC.0320
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Transcription discs
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 13 (Box 15)
    16" sound disc, Western, part 2. RESTRICTED ACCESS - Use of audio material requires production of listening copies.
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 13 (Box 15)
    16" sound disc, Eastern, parts 1 and 3. RESTRICTED ACCESS - Use of audio material requires production of listening copies.
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 20 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 20 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 20 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 20 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 27 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 27 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 27 (Box 15)
  - Al Pearce Show, 1940 Sep 27 (Box 15)
  - Arlene, Elmer, 1944 Dec 30 (Box 11)
  - Arlene, Elmer, 1944 Dec 14 (Box 12)
  - Arlene, Elmer (some Christmas gags), 1944 Dec 14 (Box 12)
  - Elmer Sells face cream, 1944 Dec 30 (Box 12)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Feb 24 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Feb 24 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Feb 3 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Feb 3 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jan 13 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Mar 17 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Mar 17 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Mar 24 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Mar 24 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 May 12 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jan 13 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jun 16 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jun 16 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jun 2 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jun 23 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Jun 23 (Box 10)
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1945 Mar 10 (Box 10)
    12" sound disc, parts 2 and ?.
  - Here Comes Elmer, 1944 Dec 23 (Box 14)